Guide to the Artmakers Records MSS.564
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. Murals, Exhibitions, and Projects, 1964-2018; 14.33 Linear Feet in 8 manuscript boxes, 3 half manuscript boxes, 5 small flat boxes, 8 oversized flat boxes, 2 rolled storage boxes, 16 flat file folders, and 6 folders in 3 oversized boxes; 1 VHS; 28.6 Gigabytes in 5096 computer files
  - Perrottet, Camille and Nick Pelafas -- PS 94/Sunset Park Mural, 2014-2016
    - Digital Files, FA_MSS_564_ER_29
    - Drawings (Flat-file-folder 10 Left, Box Shared Fales 110, Folder 10)
  - La Lucha Continua: The Struggle Continues, 1985 and 2017 Exhibition, 2016-2017
    - Correspondence, Grant Applications, Press, Notes, Exhibition Site Map, and Catalog, 2016-2017 (Box 11, Folder 10, Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Exhibition Wall Text and Layout, circa 2017 (Box 16, Folder 4, Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Photographs, circa 2017 (Box 12, Folder 2, Box 16, Folder 5-8, Box 21, Folder 7-9)
    - Interview with Chino Garcia from Charas -- Interviewed by Jane Weissman -- Filmed by Maria Dominguez, 2016; FA_MSS_564_ER_34
    - Electronic Records, FA_MSS_564_ER_28
  - Perrottet, Camille (Designer/Lead Artist) -- Welling Court Murals, 2016-2018
    - Press, 2016-2018 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Electronic Records, FA_MSS_564_ER_30
  - Unidentified Mural -- Textile Paintings of Maurice Bishop, Nanny of the Maroons, Marcus Garvey and Bob Marley, undated (Box 24)
    Rolled items must be reviewed by a conservator prior to use.